https://suncewinery.com/terms-of-use/

Terms of Use
Sunce Winery Legal Notices
Welcome to Sunce Winery and Vineyard! Sunce Winery provides products and services to you subject to the following notices, terms, and conditions. In addition, when you use any Suncé Winery service (such as purchasing wine), you will be subject to the rules, guidelines, policies, terms, and conditions applicable to such service.
We may change these terms at any time. Your continued use of Sunce Winery Web Site means that you accept our terms and conditions as we may modify them from time-to-time. You agree that your continued use of this site constitutes your acceptance of any such modifications. So please check back here from time-to-time.
For additional details, visit: Privacy Policy
Wine Purchases
To purchase wine online, you must utilize the Sunce Winery order form and provide the required information. By sending the completed form, you certify that you will provide us with accurate account information (such as your real name and a valid email address).
Restrictions On Use Of Materials
All content appearing on the Sunce Winery Web site at www.suncewinery.com, including text, graphics, logos, button icons, message boards, chats, images, audio and video clips and other features, are the copyrights, trademarks, trade dress and or other intellectual property owned, controlled or licensed by Sunce Winery. Such content is protected by copyright as a collective work or compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement and assembly) under U.S. and international copyright and other laws and are the property of Sunce Winery, its licensors, or the party credited as the provider of the content. All Sunce Winery graphics, logos and service names are trademarks of Sunce Winery, and may not be used in connection with any product or service except with the written permission of Sunce Winery, and may not be used in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among the public, or in any manner that disparages or discredits Sunce Winery, or its products or services.
You may not copy, reproduce, distribute, publish, display, perform, modify, create derivative works, transmit, or in any way exploit such content, nor may you distribute any part of such content on any other web site or any network, including a local area network, sell or offer it for sale, or use such content to create any kind of database. All software used on www.suncewinery.com is the property of Sunce Winery, or its software suppliers, and is protected by U.S. and international copyright and other laws. However, you may download from www.suncewinery.com onto a single computer such content for your own personal, noncommercial use, but only if you make one machine readable copy and/or one print copy. You may not alter or remove any copyright or other proprietary notice from copies of the content. Copying or storing any content except as provided above is expressly prohibited without the prior written permission of the copyright holder identified in the copyright notice appearing with the particular content. All requests for republication should be directed to our email.
Comments and Email Contacts
Sunce Winery enables visitors to send us comments via an emai form on the site. Should you send us an email using this online form, you automatically grant Sunce Winery (or warrant that the copyright owner of any content grants to Sunce Winery) and its affiliates a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, perform and display such reviews and comments as a whole or in part, and to incorporate it in other works in any media or technology now known or later developed throughout the universe. You also grant Sunce Winery and its affiliates permission to copy your review and comments as part of the normal backup process and archives containing your posts. You also grant Sunce Winery and its affiliates and sub-licensees the right to use the name that you submit with any review or comment, if any, in connection with such review or comment.
Copyright Complaints
Sunce Winery and its affiliates respect the intellectual property of others and we ask our users to do the same. If you believe that your work has been copied and is accessible in a way that constitutes copyright infringement or that www.suncewinery.com contains links or other references to another website that contains material or activity that infringes your copyright, please provide the Sunce Winery copyright agent the following written information via email:
An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest;
A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed upon;
A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the site;
Your address, telephone number, and email address;
A statement by you that you have a good-faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
A statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.
The Sunce Winery representative for notice of claims of copyright infringement on its site can be reached as follows:
Copyright Representative
Sunce Winery
1839 Olivet Road
Santa Rosa, CA 95401
1 (707) 526-WINE
Fax: (707) 526-5961
Privacy Policy
In addition to reviewing these Legal Notices, please read our Privacy Policy before you submit any personally identifiable information to us.
Disclaimer
THIS SITE IS PROVIDED BY SUNCE WINERY ON AN “AS IS” BASIS. SUNCE WINERY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE SITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, OR PRODUCTS INCLUDED ON THIS SITE. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, SUNCE WINERY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. SUNCE WINERY WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, EVEN IF SUNCE WINERY OR AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT PERMIT THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY OR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN NO EVENT SHALL SUNCE WINERY’S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES AND CAUSES OF ACTION (WHETHER OR NOT IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE) EXCEED THE AMOUNT PAID BY YOU, IF ANY FOR ACCESSING THIS OR ANY OTHER SUNCE WINERY SITE.
Applicable Law
This site is created and controlled by Sunce Winery, from its offices in the State of California, USA. As such, the laws of the State of California will govern these disclaimers, terms, and conditions, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws. We reserve the right to make changes to our site and these disclaimers, terms, and conditions at any time. If any provision in this Agreement is invalid or unenforceable, the remaining provisions will continue in full force and effect.
The information and materials on the Sunce Winery Web Site are presented solely for use in the United States, its territories and possessions. Those who choose to access the Sunce Winery site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.
Use By Minors
Sunce Winery Web Site is for adults of legal age in the states or territories where they reside and usage by minors is not intended. That said, the safety of children is very important to us. Children, particularly those under the age of 13, should always ask parents or guardians for permission before sending personal information to Sunce Winery or to anyone contacted through our websites.
External Links
Sunce Winery Web site contain links to outside services and resources, and Sunce Winery does not control the availability or content of such sites. Any concerns you may have concerning the operation or content of such service or resource should therefore be directed to its site administrator or webmasters, as the case may be.
Our Address
Sunce Winery & Vineyard
1839 Olivet Road
Santa Rosa, CA 95401
1 (707) 526-WINE (9463)
Scroll to top
